ジュイス？ またやっちゃったみたいなの
Juiz, it looks like I did it again.
人を？
Did you kill someone?
ええ
Yes. I think it's the usual place.
場所もいつものところだと思うわ
特定しました。ルームナンバー1109
We've narrowed down your location.
Room number 1109.
事後処理をお願いできるかしら？
Would you mind cleaning up the scene?
方法は任せるけど、可能な限りエレガントに
Feel free to do whatever's necessary,
but try to do it as elegantly as possible.
心得ております
Acknowledged. Noblesse Oblige.
ノブレス・オブリージュ
今後も、貴女様が救世主たらんことを
A dying scream makes no sound
We live a dying dream...
Please continue your work as a Savior.
Callin' out to all that I've ever known
If you know what I mean...
Here am I, lost and found...
It's all that I've ever known...
Callin' out to all
It's all that I've ever known
Episode 5
Even though now isn't the
time to think about that
Catch the wheel that breaks a butterfly
Looks like I was involved in this troublesome game before I lost my memories.
Cry the rain that fills the ocean wide
If I think of it as selling my life to this "Mr. Outside" guy for ten billion yen, it's a pretty good deal.
I tried to talk with God to no avail
結構なもんだけど
http://animetranscripts.wikispaces.com
ミスター・アウトサイドって奴に100億で命を売ったと思えば
ちっくっしょー！ む、か、つ、くっ！
Calling him up in-and-out of nowhere
記憶をなくす前に
既にやっかいなゲームに巻き込まれちまってたわけか…
Damn it!
It's pissing me off!
I said if you won't save me
つうか誰だよ、ミスター・アウトサイドって！？
Who the heck is this Mr. Outside in the first place?!
Please don't waste my time
I won't be happy until I've socked him one!
そんなふざけた野郎、ぶん殴らなきゃ納得いかな…
あぶねえ、あぶねえ
That was close...
I bet I'd be killed by that so-called Supporter if I really threw it away.
これ捨てたらサポーターってのに殺されるんだっけ
Takizawa... Akira?
滝沢…朗
You bastard!
コノヤロ〜〜！
You! You! You! You! You! You!
この、この、このこのこの…
Who are you?
何だよ、お前？ サポーターか？
The Supporter?
アンタのせいだーっ！
It's all your fault!
What are you raving about all of a sudden?
何だ、やぶから棒に？
とぼけんな！
Stop playing dumb!
Do you know what kind of lives we've led for the past two months?!
この二ヶ月、俺たちがどんな目に遭ったと思ってんだ！？
You said that you were taking us to a shopping paradise, but you actually dumped us in the middle of a desert!
消費の楽園に連れてくとか言って
砂漠のど真ん中に置き去りにしやがって！
After that, the Indian site foreman scolded us, calling us weak and useless!
あの後、俺たちはインド人の現場監督に
「ひ弱だ。役立たずだ」と罵られ
We had no money and no idea what was going on;
but somehow survived, hungry and miserable every day.
金もなく、訳も分からないまま
ひもじく惨めな日々を生き延びてきたんだぞォ…
Who are you?
お前、誰？
もしかして、記憶を…？
Don't tell me, your memory...
Oh well.
もういいや
肉まん
They're meat buns.
俺、来月結婚するんだ。向こうの女性と。
Next month I'm getting married to a girl I met there.
I don't know what you intended by sending us to Dubai,
アンタがどういうつもりで俺たちをドバイに送ったのかは知らんけど
but at any rate, I was able to reintegrate myself into society thanks to you.
少なくとも俺はそのおかげで社会復帰できたんだからな
じゃ
See ya.
何なんだよ…
What's going on?
Sorry to make you do this even though you've got an interview soon.
悪いなぁ、これから面談って時に
I just don't have the knack for it.
どうも俺、そういうセンスなくってさぁ
It's fine. I usually do this anyway.
いいよ。いつものことだから
これ、咲の自画像を参考にしたんだ
Saki, I made these based on your self-portraits.
They'll probably say some harsh things during the interview.
面談では、たぶん厳しいこと言われると思うけど
そこが踏ん張りどころだから
You must stand firm when that happens.
でもな、もしどうしても我慢できなくなったら
無理しなくてもいいからなッ
However, don't force yourself to do so if you really can't stand what they say.
What do you mean?
どういう意味？
We'll take care of you until you find a job that you really want.
お前が本当にやりたいことが見つかるまで
俺たちで面倒を見てやる
これ以上は迷惑かけらんないよ…
I don't want to trouble you two any more.
You're no trouble at all, you're family.
迷惑なんて思ってないよ。家族なんだから
Should you really be saying that now...
いま、それ言うかな…
I'm hurting because of that kindness.
その優しさが痛いんだってば…
咲ちゃん
Saki-chan.
Morning.
おっはよ
Sorry, I didn't notice you.
ごめん、気づかなかった
You don't look like your usual self.
なんか大杉くんじゃないみたい
就活中って全然会わなかったっけ？
Probably because we haven't met up at all since we've been job hunting.
そうだね
I guess so.
It feels as if it's been a long time since we last met up.
なんかすごく久しぶりって感じ
Even though we just went on a graduation trip together.
この前、一緒に卒業旅行いったのに…
Did you hear what happened to Hirasawa?
平澤の話、聞いた？
あいつ、計画留年だって
He plans to postpone his graduation.
It seems that he decided to do so when we were in New York.
俺たちがニューヨーク行ってる間に決めたらしい
そっか
I see.
I had the feeling he'd do that when he said that he wouldn't go on the graduation trip.
旅行いかないって言った時から
何かそんな気はしてたんだけど
I guess so.
まあね
ゆくゆくは起業しようってことで始めたサークルだったから
He started the club because he wants to start his own company someday.
I understand how he feels.
気持ちは分かるけど
But you can only make that choice if your family is rich.
実家が金持ちじゃなきゃできない選択だよ
あいつは僕らの世代は性根がニートだからって
He said that people from our generation are NEETs by nature,
so we feel ashamed of ourselves about all sorts of things, right?
色んなことを卑下するじゃない？
I reckon that he's more than qualified to be a working adult.
でも、充分社会人として勝負できると思うんだ
本当は平澤、六個も内定取ってるんだよ。
言わないだけでさ
Hirasawa actually had six interviews lined up.
He just didn't tell us.
Oddly enough, there are cases where people like him complain when they reach 30 or 40
でも案外そんな奴が、三十、四十になって
that society can't accept them.
コミットできなかった社会に愚痴をこぼすようになることもあるんだよ
I don't want Hirasawa to end up like that.
僕は平澤にそんな奴になってほしくないんだ
Don't you agree?
そう思わない？
大杉くんの言ってることは正しいと思う
I think what you said is right.
Saki-chan, are you free after your interview?
咲ちゃん！
今日、内定者面談終わった後、時間ある？
What for?
どうして？
U-Um...
あの…二人で食事とかしない？
Why don't we have lunch together?
卒業と就職のお祝い、両方兼ねてさ
To celebrate being able to graduate and find a job.
Let's treat ourselves to an expensive lunch since we're both wearing suits.
お互いスーツだし、ちょっと奮発して
I should be done by 2 P.M., so I'll come and pick you up.
僕は二時には終わると思うから、迎えに行くよ
よしっ！
All right!
おめでとうございます
Congratulations!
晴れてルールを思い出されたわけですね
You were forced to remember the rules, right?
I didn't remember them by myself.
思い出してはいないんだけどさ
日本を救えって言われたって
漠然としすぎじゃん、そんなの
But asking me to save Japan is a bit vague, isn't it?
で、実際どこまでできるもんなのかなって思ってさ
So, I want to know the limits of what you can do.
What do you mean by "limits?"
どこまで、と言いますと？
How should I put this...
なんつーか、例えば
For example, only a few people can give out cellphones charged with ten billion yen able to do anything, right?
100億までなら何でもできる携帯配れる人間なんて
そうそういると思えないだろ？
日本でも、総理大臣とかさ
In Japan, only the Prime Minister or someone like him could do that, probably.
I reckon it's impossible unless he's the most important person in the country.
何か、一番偉い人とかじゃないと無理な気がするわけ、俺的には
So, could you make someone like the Prime Minister cry for mercy?
で、その総理大臣とかをギャフンと言わせることはできるのか、とかさ
お前は気楽でいいな…
It's great to be carefree like you.
受理されました
Request accepted. Noblesse Oblige.
ノブレス・オブリージュ。テレビの前でお待ちください
Please wait in front of a television.
貴方が救世主たらんことを
Please continue your work as a Savior.
テレビって…
Television...?
資料によると
Based on the data we have,
the missiles used during the Careless Monday incident were likely the missiles recently deployed to the Navy.
迂闊な月曜日事件で使用されたミサイルは
海上自衛隊が新たに配備したミサイルの可能性を示唆している
総理は、主要都市に落ちたミサイルが
Mr. Prime Minister, you knew that the missiles launched at the major cities were from Navy stock, right?
海自の巡航ミサイルだったと
知っていたんじゃないんですか？
Lower House Budget Management
and Observation Committee
PRP - Sewa Policy Research Group
Yamamoto Osamu
Additionally, we have information that a group of terrorists called "Selecao" are behind this incident!
Relay
さらに、事件を引き起こしたテロリストが
セレソンと名乗る組織であるとの情報もあるんですよ！
内閣総理大臣
Prime Minister.
Lower House Budget Management
and Observation Committee
Relay from the First Lower
House Committee Meeting Room
Mercy.
ギャフン
We can't hear you!
聞こえねーよー！
Mercy.
Prime Minister
Eda Kazuhiko
ギャフン
そういうことじゃねえんだけどさー！
That's not what I meant!
まあ、実力は分かったけど。とはいえなー
Well, now I know what this thing is capable of... I guess...
森美咲…
Morimi Saki...
ああ、やっべえ！
昨日来てたメール、ほったらかしててまだ読んでねえし！
Oh no!
The message came in yesterday and I haven't read it yet!
I went home without saying anything this
morning, but did something happen? It
seemed like your lost memories came
back, but I'm sending you a text because
I'm still worried.
Reply
"I went home without saying anything this morning
「今朝は黙って帰っちゃったけど
もしかして何かあった!?」
but did something happen?"
Function
I went home without saying anything this
morning, but did something happen? It
seemed like your lost memories came
back, but I'm sending you a text because
I'm still worried.
Reply
Function
I went home without saying anything this
morning, but did something happen? It
seemed like your lost memories came
back, but I'm sending you a text because
I'm still worried.
Reply
Function
I went home without saying anything this
morning, but did something happen? It
seemed like your lost memories came
back, but I'm sending you a text because
I'm still worried.
Reply
Function
I went home without saying anything this
morning, but did something happen? It
seemed like your lost memories came
back, but I'm sending you a text because
I'm still worried.
Reply
Function
心配かけちゃったなぁ
> I went home without saying anything this
> morning, but did something happen? It
> seemed like your lost memories came
> back, but I'm sending you a text because
> I'm still worried.
Send
Select
Attach
Function
Guess I worried her...
Character
Close
Confirm
滝沢くん？
Takizawa-kun?
"Sorry I didn't watch the late show with you.
「レイトショーに行けなくてごめん
記憶は戻りませんが元気です
Haven't recovered my memories, but I'm doing okay.
By the way, can we meet up now?
ところで今から会えませんか？
There's something I want to ask you."
聞きたいことがあるのです」って…
今は無理だよ…
It's impossible right now.
来ねえな。怒ってんのかな？
She's not replying.
I guess she's angry. I'll have to apologize in person.
直に謝りに行くか
ジュイス
Juiz, it's about the girl that was with me yesterday.
昨日一緒にいた女の子なんだけどさ
Yeah.
国会中継見たか？
Did you watch the Diet session?
ギャフン一つで支持率10％アップだとさ
The approval rating went up ten percent with just a single "mercy"...
It was only worth sixty yen?
Switch
Display
Function
Selecao Activity History
Refresh
History
Delete
Make the PM say "Mercy"
Shuto Expwy Rt 5 Ikebukuro
Line Bijoki Toll Plaza
Tokyo Gaikan Expwy Izumi
Toll Plaza
60円で上がる程度の船か…
New history update
Selecao Activity History
Refresh
History
Delete
Make the PM say "Mercy"
Shuto Expwy Rt 5 Ikebukuro
Line Bijoki Toll Plaza
Tokyo Gaikan Expwy Izumi
Toll Plaza
Seleção Activity History
Refresh
History
Delete
Make the PM say "Mercy"
Shuto Expwy Rt 5 Ikebukuro
Line Bijoki Toll Plaza
Tokyo Gaikan Expwy Izumi
Toll Plaza
Switch
Display
Function
Seleção Activity History
Refresh
History
Delete
Find that girl from
yesterday
Make the PM say "Mercy"
Shuto Expwy Rt 5 Ikebukuro
Line Bijoki Toll Plaza
Juiz, it's me.
ジュイス、私だ
プロのモデルになりたいなら
Don't eat if you want to become a professional model.
貴方たちはやめておきなさいね
It'll be easier if you always show some restraint.
普段から節制しておいた方が楽でしょ？
あら、ナンバー９
Oh, No. 9.
復活してからずいぶんアプローチを変えてきたわね
You've changed your approach since your rebirth.
誰か国会中継見た？
Who saw the Diet session?
I wonder what No. 1 will do now that this happened.
これを受けてナンバー１はどうするのかしら？
A realist versus an idealist.
リアリストとロマンチスト
どっちの味方に付く気もないけれど
I don't intend to make either of them my ally, but the cuter one is...
キュートなのは
あ、そうだ
Oh yeah, is there anything scheduled for tonight?
今日の夜、何か予定入ってる？
There is.
はい
もしかしたら私、突然姿を消すかもしれないけど
I might disappear suddenly, so don't lose sight of me.
絶対に見失わないで
Okay...
今夜また、やっちゃいそうな気がするから
I have a feeling that I'll be doing it again tonight.
You're lucky.
運がよかったねえ
そんな事件を生き延びた君から見て
As a survivor of that incident,
how do you feel about the recent missile attack?
今度のミサイルテロはどう映っていますか？
忌憚のない意見を聞かせてほしいなぁ
I want to hear your honest opinion.
Ah...
結構、若い人は歓迎ムードなんでしょ？
迂闊な月曜日は
Youngsters welcomed the Careless Monday incident, right?
あの
Um...
今までは犠牲者が出なかったですから
The previous incidents didn't have any casualties,
そういった軽率な意見もあったと思うんです
so I had that rash thought about it too.
でも、おとといの攻撃では被害者も出ているわけですから
However, there were casualties during the attack that took place two days ago.
お悔やみの気持ちとともに…
Due to that, I felt sympathetic and—
That's enough. Thank you.
ああ、もういいや。ありがとう
I see. A surprisingly average answer.
そっか…案外普通なんだねえ
いやね、これからの社会を背負って立つ若者から
Look, I wanted to hear the frank opinions of you youngsters who are about to join society.
率直な意見が聞きたかったわけ
I'm not looking for a textbook answer.
杓子定規な正論じゃなく
でもまあ、何にせよ無事でよかった
Well, it's great that you were unharmed.
You can do anything as long as you're alive.
命さえあれば人生なんとかなるよ
Anyway, since you came all the way here, why don't we go for lunch a bit early?
よし！
じゃあ、せっかく来てもらったことだし
少し早いけどランチでもどう？
評判なんだよ、うちの社食
The canteen here has a good reputation.
Meeting Room #13
はい！
Okay!
This is weird...
おかしいなぁ…
場所違うのかなぁ…
Did I go to the wrong place?
すいません…
Sorry.
いえ、大丈夫です！ 大丈夫ですから
It's okay. I'm fine.
I'm really okay.
見た～？ さっきの牛丼の子
Did you see the girl that had the beef bowl spilled on her?
I did!
見た見た！
久しぶりじゃない？ 部長があの手使うの
It's been a while since the section chief used that.
Yeah.
ホントだよね～
Even though the section chief was pretty evil,
that girl was pretty dense too.
でも、部長もたいがい悪人だけど
あの子も相当鈍いよねー
She was made to wait for nearly an hour for nothing; if she'd noticed that sooner,
一時間近くほったらかされた時点で気づいてれば
牛丼まで掛けらんなくて済んだのに
she wouldn't have had a beef bowl spilled on her.
Provided that she had a clue about what was going on.
空気読んでればね～
Going on a trip at a time like this and coming back only a day before the interview;
っていうか、このご時世に面談前日まで
旅行いってるって時点でアウトだけど
that's why she was rejected.
今どき、コネだけで入れると思ってる方が甘くない？
Wouldn't you agree that it's a bit naïve to think that you can get in just by using your connections these days?
Choco Coronet
Just leave me alone!
「もうほっといて」はないと思ったけど
やっぱやるわ、あの子
Well, I don't think we can leave her alone,
but I guess she did her best.
山月パンでございます
This is Sangetsu Bakery.
Yes.
はい。ええ！ この度は妹がお世話になりまして
Ah, thanks for taking care of my sister!
あ、はい…はい
Yes.
Yes...
そうですか…
I see...
はい。はい、伝えておきます
Yes. Yes. I'll tell her.
わざわざありがとうございました
Thanks for calling.
はい。失礼します
Yes. Goodbye.
Just leave me alone!
一昨日のこと、謝りたかったし
I came to apologize for what happened two days ago.
Also, there's something I wanted to ask you,
できれば教えてほしいこともあったんで
so I came to find you.
直接来ちゃった
咲…ちゃん？
Saki... chan...
断られて当然なんだよね？
It was obvious that I'd be rejected.
最初の内定者面談に行けなかったことも
Since I missed the first interview, I thought that it would be fine if I sincerely apologized.
誠心誠意謝ればなんとかなると思ったし
そのチャンスがもらえたと思ってたけど…
I thought they'd given me another chance.
やっぱ、そんなに甘くなかった…
Things just aren't that simple.
でもさ、だからって牛丼掛けなくたっていいと思うんだ
Even so, I don't think there was any need to spill a beef bowl on me...
Even though it's hard to reject me out of consideration for my brother-in-law,
兄さんの手前断りにくいにしても
he's an adult. If he could call himself an upstanding member of society,
大人なんだから
自分たちこそ立派な社会人なんだって言うんなら
couldn't he have just told me right to my face?!
はっきり言えばいいじゃん！
Honestly, there's another company I wanted to work for.
私、本当は行きたい会社があったの
でも面接でね
「あなたたち若い世代こそが社会の主人公です」って言うくせに
However, during the interview, even though they said that "society belongs to you youngsters",
I felt that they really just wanted to use us so that things would continue smoothly for them. So I refused.
実際は私たちを使って、自分たちだけ上手くやっていこうとしている
だけなんじゃないかって思えてきちゃって
自分から断ったの…
バカなことしたかな？
Did I do something stupid?
でももう、うちにも戻れない…
But I can't head home now...
I really like my sister and my niece...
お姉ちゃんのことも、姪っ子のことも大好きだけど
Even though I like Ryousuke-san... I really like him...
良介さんのことが好き…大好きなの…
It hurts because I really like them!
大好きだから辛いの…！
You're welcome to stay at my place.
うちへおいでよ。全部俺が背負いこんでやるから
I'll take care of everything.
咲の話で俺が何すりゃいいのかも分かったし
Saki, I finally know what I should do after listening to what you said.
That's why you don't need to force yourself to work.
だから無理して働くことないよ
Leave it to me.
俺に任せて！
After all, this country has fallen into such a sad state that someone needs to stand up and lead it somewhere.
それに、この国はどのみち一旦は誰かが何とかしなきゃならないほど
おかしなことになってんだからさ
Save the country with just ten billion?
100億やるからこの国を救えだって？
いい加減にも程があるよ
There's a limit to how absurd things can be.
だからジョニーはああなったんだ
That's why I was running around with my Johnny exposed...
だからいいんだよ、咲も働かなくて
That's why, Saki, it's fine for you not to work.
いずれ困るのはあいつらさ
Someday, they'll be the ones who will be worrying.
It's okay for you to not do anything until that happens.
だから、それまでは何もしなくていいんだ
あなた…本当は誰なの？
Just... who are you?
I don't know. But I'll probably know in the future.
分かんない。でもたぶん、これから分かるよ
大杉さん、いい加減わけを教えてくださいよ！
Oosugi-san, enough already. Please tell me what happened.
I'm just your junior at the university, and I don't intend our connection to be anything other than that.
僕はあなたと後輩以上の関係になるつもりは…
何を勘違いしてんだ？
What are you blabbering about?
Everyone has to become a working adult someday.
誰もがいずれは社会人になるんだ
It won't hurt my wallet to go to one or two three-star restaurants!
三つ星の一つやふたつ、行っといても損はないだろッ！
ほらぁっ！
Hey!
Why did you choose me?!
だからって、なんで僕なんですか！？
八万もしたんだ…吐いてたまるか！
I paid eighty thousand yen for this,
there's no way I'm going to puke it out!
Crap, what have I been doing all this time?
くそっ、今まで何やってたんだ！？
Tell me if you already have a boyfriend!
男がいるなら言ってくれよ！
I'd have backed off if you'd done that!
そうすりゃ俺だって、さっさと身を引いたのに！
夜は封印
戸惑い混じれば終わる
迷い出すぐらいならいっそ
わ     け
理由も捨てよう
また夢に溺れる
不確かに続いてく未来
まだ君を許せる
意味を知れる
耳を澄ますための夜
その理由を真似て変われる
君の呼吸を知るために
未来の根を切っても構わない